yeah i'm pretty sure there's actually nothing about oil in nigeria it probably has to do with
one of two things one an attempt to manufacture a global war between christians and muslims i mean
the way they are going so hard trying to make this happen you have to be like stop stop trying
to make fetch fetch or two so ecowas is the economic community of west african states but
it really is just a fancy name for let's put together these 15 african countries that we
the colonizers and the central bank can steal from them easily and it includes nigeria along with
niger burkina faso and mali which coincidentally borders nigeria now recently niger mali and
burkina faso said you know what ecowas go ecowas yourself because we're going to join our own squad
called the sahel alliance and we're going to kick france out and take our resources back
well the other members of the ecowas community instead of saying we're going to rock with you
said how dare you do this to our colonizer so i feel like this could also just be a tactic to be
on the ground and in the region to stir up some nonsense with the sahel alliance because for other
members of ecowas for instance cameroon whose president was just sworn in for the eighth time
baby he's 92 for those corrupt leaders they looking at the sahel alliance like we gotta get
them out of here they messing up the coon coins burkina faso's leader ibram traore just took over
the one year tenure because every year they switch like who's going to be the head of it and which is
a great idea and um yeah he literally did a speech where he was like we're about to be facing the black
winter because these folks are about to try and come for us and i know that it's very difficult
when you have a bunch of people rocking together to like keep everything copacetic but don't sweat it
don't fret it we squad that's my interpretation translation for y'all so yes nigeria has oil
nigeria also has a puppet in power and if you think puppets in power won't put their people in jeopardy
in order to maintain their position of power then you don't know nothing about power but we about
to learn because it's time to take our power back